sprezzabox.com 2015-06-19

# PRIVACY - SprezzaBox

### Your privacy is important to SprezzaBox. 

This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that SprezzaBox collects, and the ways in which SprezzaBox uses that personal information.  
Personal information collection  
SprezzaBox may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * Information about your use of this website (including all activity that directed you to and from SprezzaBox.com and all activities performed while on said site)
  * Information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website
  * About transactions carried out over this website
  * Information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services. 

### Using personal information

SprezzaBox may use your personal information to: 

  * administer this website;
  * Personalize the website for you;
  * Enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send to you statements and invoices;
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you marketing communications.

Where SprezzaBox discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, SprezzaBox may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

### Securing your data

SprezzaBox will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.  
SprezzaBox will store all the personal information you provide (on Chargify secure servers).  
[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be  protected by encryption technology.

###   
Cross-border data transfers

Information that SprezzaBox collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which SprezzaBox operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world. You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

### Updating this statement

SprezzaBox may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

### Other websites

This website contains links to other websites. SprezzaBox is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

###  Contact SprezzaBox

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or SprezzaBox's treatment of your personal information, please contact us via our Contact Us page on this website.
